Hello, I'm Jake Archibald. I'm a developer advocate for Google Chrome.
Hola, soy Jake Archibald. Soy un developer advocate de Google Chrome.
And I'm delighted to tell you about an exciting event taking place in Brazil in August.
Y tengo el placer de informarle acerca de un evento emocionante que tendrá lugar en Brasil en agosto.
That's right, the Olympics.
Si, los Juegos Olímpicos.
Which features people who are the best in the world throwing things,
La presentación de las mejores personas del mundo que lanzan cosas,
sometimes themselves
a veces ellos mismos
Kicking things, sometimes each other
chutando coisas, às vezes uns aos outros
And travelling really fast, sometimes on top of a bike,
Y todo esto muy rápidamente, a veces en una bicicleta,
or sometimes, a horse.
o, a veces en un caballo.
But after all, let's over. On the 26 and 27 of August is BrazilJS Conf in Porto Alegre.
Pero después de todo, vamos a tener más. El 26 y el 27 de agosto es el BrazilJS Conf en Porto Alegre.
I'm gonna be there, along with a bunch of people much smarter than me,
Yo estaré allí, junto con un montón de gente más inteligente que yo,
And I'll be talking about the future of Web performance.
Y voy a estar hablando sobre el futuro de la Web performance.
And what is that involved? Well, you have to join me and find out.
Y lo que será? Bueno, usted tiene que unirse a mí y averiguarlo.
I mean, I haven't written yet, so I really have no idea.
Es decir, no he escrito, por lo que no tengo mucha idea.